<!DOCTYPE html
  SYSTEM "about:legacy-compat">
<html xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" xmlns:tei="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0" lang="it">
   <head>
      <meta http-equiv="Content-Type" content="text/html; charset=UTF-8">
      <title>Catalogo Cicognara Number 2530</title>
      <link rel="stylesheet" href="../../assets/item-pages.css">
   </head>
   <body>
      <header id="metadata">
         <ul>
            <li xmlns="">Views in Egypt [microform] : from the original drawings in the possession of Sir Robert
               Ainslie, taken during his embassy to Constantinople by Luigi Mayer / engraved by and
               under the direction of Thomas Milton ; with historical observations, and incidental
               illustrations of the manners and customs of the natives of that country.</li>
            <li xmlns="">Views in Egypt, from the original drawings in the possession of Sir Robert Ainslie,
               taken during his embassy to Constantinople, by Luigi Mayer. Engraved by and under
               the direction of Thomas Milton. With historical observations, and incidental illustrations,
               of the manners and customs of the natives of that country.</li>
            <li xmlns="">Views in Palestine [microform] : from the original drawings of Luigi Mayer : with
               an historical and descriptive account of the country, and its remarkable places =
               Vues en Palestine : d'après les dessins originaux de Luigi Mayer : avec une relation
               historique et descriptive du pay et des lieux principaux qu'on y remarque.</li>
            <li xmlns="">Views in the Ottoman empire [microform] : chiefly in Caramania, a part of Asia Minor
               hitherto unexplored : with some curious selections from the islands of Rhodes and
               Cyprus, and the celebrated cities of Corinth, Carthage, and Tripoli : from the original
               drawings in the possession of Sir R. Ainslie, taken during his embassy to Constantinople
               by Luigi Mayer : with historical observations and incidental illustrations of the
               manners and customs of the natives of the country.</li>
            <li xmlns="">Views in the Ottoman empire, chiefly in Caramania, a part of Asia Minor hitherto unexplored;
               with some curious selections from the islands of Rhodes and Cyprus, and the celebrated
               cities of Corinth, Carthage, and Tripoli: from the original drawings in the possession
               of Sir R. Ainslie, taken during his embassy to Constantinople, by Luigi Mayer: with
               historical observations and incidental illustrations of the manners and customs of
               the natives of the country.</li>
         </ul>
      </header>
   </body>
</html>